Slipstream is a fantasy, drama film directed by Anthony Hopkins.
Aging screenwriter Felix Bonhoeffer has lived his life in two states
of existence: in reality and his own interior world.
While working on a murder mystery script, and unaware that his brain is on the verge of implosion,
Felix is baffled when his characters start to appear in his life, and vice versa.
Felix Bonhoeffer, played by Anthony Hopkins.
Gina, played by Stella Arroyave.
Lily, played by Lana Antonova.
Shelly's Sister, played by Lindsay Barth.
Mort / Phil Henderson / Patrolman, played by Michael Clarke Duncan.
Bonnie, played by S. Epatha Merkerson.
Slipstream is a 2007 American film starring, written, scored, and directed by Anthony Hopkins, which explores the
premise of a screenwriter who is caught in a slipstream of time, memories, fantasy and reality.
The film co-stars and was produced by Hopkins' wife
Stella Arroyave, who also plays his wife.
The film premiered at the 2007 Sundance Film Festival.
Hopkins composed the music for the film, while British composer
Harry Gregson-Williams scored and produced it.
The tone is emotional.